digitalbloggers.com 2019-12-13

# Privacy Policy

The Digital blogger Privacy Policy is here to help you understand how we use the information you provide to us so you can have complete confidence when using our platform. Your privacy is very important to us. We want to make your experience on the Internet as enjoyable and rewarding as possible.

We will notify you of changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new policy on this page so you can stay informed of our practices, as they may change in the future.

### Your Information

By visiting our site or sending us information, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. Your assent to these practices is essential for us to continue operating this website.

The personal information we collect includes your name and email address. We use the information that we collect to provide our services, send you our newsletter if you’ve opted in, contact you regarding new promotions, and to improve our site.

When submitting any information on our website you expressly authorize us to use your personal information as explained in this privacy policy, and you consent to receiving commercial email from us, Digital Bloggers, which is owned by Six Figure Mentors (SFM) and Digital Experts Academy (DEA). You can expect to receive newsletters, promotions, and other similar offers. Should you wish to discontinue receiving these e-mailings simply unsubscribe using the link in the email you receive.

### Cookies and Other Automatic Info We Collect

A cookie is a very small text document which includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a website, that site’s computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies.

We automatically collect certain information from visitors to this site, such as Internet addresses browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring and exit page, operating system, time-stamps, and click-stream data. We also track and analyse non-identifying and aggregate usage and volume statistical information from our visitors and customers. This information is logged to help diagnose technical problems, and to administer our site so that we can constantly improve it.

Anything you send us, post on our site, or use with our service, such as blog postings or videos, or if others send us anything about your activities or postings, we may collect such information into a file specific to you. We use this information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, and enforce our customer agreements.

We take measures to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of your information by carefully limiting access to the database in which your personal information is stored. We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. For example, we may disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of wrongful conduct.

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, nor do we knowingly distribute such information. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from someone under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records.

Contact us at the address below if you want us to change or delete any information that we have about you. We will respond to your request to access, update, or delete your information within ten (10) business days. Before we are able to provide you with any information, correct any inaccuracies, or delete any information, however, we may ask you to verify your identity.

The Digital Bloggers website is owned and operated, or operated under agreement, by:

Digital Experts, LLC  
228 Park Ave S, #11107, New York, NY 10003
